<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Hannes Lehmann</title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://hanneslehmann.github.io/tags/cxm/index.xml/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <author>Hannes Lehmann</author>
    <copyright>2014 Hannes Lehmann</copyright>
    <updated>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer experience management</title>
      <link>http://hanneslehmann.github.io/2014/11/cem_01_en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      <author>Hannes Lehmann</author>
      <guid>http://hanneslehmann.github.io/2014/11/cem_01_en/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It seems that we are back to the future: 2015 will be the year where discussions about Customer Experience Management will gain even more speed. A lot of companies are trying to push tools out to the space.
They adress challenges of our new and modern world:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;30 years ago, there were small local shops (in Germany so called &amp;ldquo;Tante Emma Laden&amp;rdquo;), they knew you as a customer and most of the time even your needs. They knew even your family and possibly have seen you growing and growing to an adult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, when you stepped in once a week, they were already prepared with your usual shopping list&amp;hellip;and when it was sommer - they put some sun blocker on top. Possibly they remembered you&amp;rsquo;ve broken your sun glasses last sommer, asking you if you want to buy one. On the other days, they already prepared you the right news-paper. And when it was week-end, it was time for your favorite &amp;ldquo;Croissant&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nowadays this intense relationship to the customer got lost - and what do you do? You try to collect as much data as possible to gain insights of the customer: the feelings, the (actual) needs and even predictions what she/he might need in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tibco is placing the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.tibco.com/company/news/releases/2014/tibco-announces-its-new-marketing-application-built-to-optimize-consumer-engagement?adbsc=social_engage__20140910_31264846&#34;&gt;Engage Platform&lt;/a&gt; into the bet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>